Milkman, washerman, watchman, Kamlabai, everyone's numbers,
phone charger on the fridge, laptop charger, check wallet,
madam, you are set, you go and Han
ji's health has deteriorated a lot, so I have
all the hospital numbers too,
my dear, you just concentrate on your business trip
and go to Goa without any hesitation, even if there is an
emergency here, she is there to take care of me, right?
[Music] She
is there, right? Why do I have to go
out for 4 days for any work, have
you
even found someone to take care of me,
who is she?
[Music]
I will take care, I am talking about you, madam
[laughs]
[Music]
₹5000 plus network hospitals, search
hospitals nearby
[Music]
you take care of all your insurance